Kenny Downs

Web Developer

San Francisco, CA kennvdownsweb@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/kennv-downs-sf

Github: github.com/krdowns
Website: www.kridowns.com

Summary

Front-end Focused Web Developer with a passion for interaction-oriented design and development, problem-solving, and meaningful experiences. Good eye for design and empathetic to the needs of a user. Service-minded, specializing in finding creative, helpful solutions to the problems people face every day, no matter how big or small.

Skills

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Node.js, Mongoose, MongoDB, Express, Git, Github, User Stories, ERDs, Responsive Design, OOP, MVC Pattern, WireFraming, Python, React

Relevant Experience

October 2018 - February 2019

General Assembly, San Francisco - Web Development Student

- Full-Time Full Stack Web Development Immersive
- Capstone Project See

January 22, 2019 - February 4, 2019

- o HTML, CSS, JQuery, Node.js, Watson Tone Analyzer API, Chart.js, Moment.js
- Monument Project

November 3, 2018 - November 5, 2018

o HTML, CSS Landing Page

Experience

October 2015 - PRESENT

Towne Park, Atlanta, GA/San Francisco, CA - Guest Service Captain/Account Manager

- Interacted with patients as they arrive and depart Cancer Treatment Center.
- Handled payroll, budgeting, and employee onboarding and training.
- Corresponded with regional management in weekly Zoom meetings.

July 2013 - May 2015

Troup County Parks and Recreation, LaGrange, GA - Front Desk Associate

- Interacted with 50-100 customers on a daily basis, and maintained customer database.
- Informed guests and members of upcoming programs and classes.

Education

General Assembly, San Francisco, CA - Web Development Immersive Certificate	2019
Berklee College of Music, Boston, MA – Bachelor of Arts in Music Production	2017
Hillsong Leadership College, Sydney, Australia – Cert IV in Worship Arts	2012